pluggedinonline.com 2008-08-28

# Privacy Policy/Terms of Use

## Privacy Policy

[](http://www.whitsend.org/library/privacy.cfm)Greetings from Focus on the Family and welcome to our site! We extend the following information to assure you, our guest, that we are concerned about and respect your privacy while visiting our Web site. Focus on the Family will never sell, lease or rent your confidential information. However, if it is necessary, we will share information for legal reasons. We will always endeavor to take steps to assure that any information you provide to us will remain secure. We want you to feel safe in your online experience while visiting our site. We therefore request that you take a moment to review the following valuable information.

## Collection of Information 

Focus on the Family does not collect personal information without your knowledge during your visit to our Web sites. However, Focus on the Family does at times ask that you provide us with personal information while online. The type of information we collect typically, but not always, corresponds directly with the service you request. For instance, you can make donations, when requested you can offer your thoughts, opinions, prayers, concerns, ideas, personal experiences, questions and/or suggestions to our resources, contests, or radio broadcasts, or you can request that a resource be sent to you directly from our Online Resource Center. As a visitor, the personal information you provide may also be used to improve the usability of, and information available on, our sites. In other words, at times we will ask you for more information, beyond just your name and contact information, than is needed to facilitate our response to your specific request. Your provision of such additional information is your acknowledgement that you consent to our use of such information to better serve you, our visitor, and others coming to our sites. We also have a [Privacy Policy for Children](http://www.whitsend.org/library/privacy.cfm) that parents may be interested in reviewing.

Focus on the Family does not sell, lease or rent your confidential information. However, we may need to disclose personal information as required by law, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, search warrant, in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a law enforcement agency request, to enforce our Terms of Service, or site rules; or to protect the safety and security of our visitors and our sites.

## Security

Our Web site's ecommerce system uses SSL encryption to protect sensitive data transmissions from your computer to our Web site. You are able to see when the SSL encryption is active either by the "padlock" icon at the bottom of your browser's window or by a blue line around the window. In certain areas, password protection is used to protect your privacy and security. 

## Changes

Focus reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time and requests that you review this policy for updates. 

## Questions or Suggestions 

Please direct all questions or comments regarding this privacy policy to Focus at (800) A-FAMILY (232-6459) or write us at Focus on the Family, Colorado Springs, Colorado 80995. **This Web site may provide links to external Web sites maintained by individuals or organizations external to Focus on the Family. Once you access information that links you to another Web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the Web site containing the information you have linked to.**

## Additional Information About Our Online Resource Center:

**Cookies:** A small piece of data that a website can store on your system is referred to as a "cookie." Cookies are often used to enhance your online experience. Many browsers recognize when a cookie has been sent to your computer and will give you the option to refuse or allow it. Within the Online Resource Center, we use two different cookies. Below are details regarding how these two cookies are used by our web site. Please be aware that we do not use cookies to track a user's navigation through our Web site.

**Account Registration:** When you request a resource we require that you provide us certain information that allows us to complete your transaction. This information is used to create a unique account within our Online Resource Center. Following account registration, a "cookie" is used to automatically identify you as a registered user when you are browsing the Online Resource Center (you have the option of declining this cookie during account registration if desired). 

**Shopping Cart Identification:** The Shopping Cart Identification "cookie" allows the Online Resource Center to connect you to your active shopping cart. This cookie is set to expire whenever you exit your current browser session.

## Terms and Conditions of Use

We have taken every effort to design our Web sites to be useful, informative, helpful, honest and fun. Hopefully we've accomplished that — and would ask that you let us know if you'd like to see improvements or changes that would make it even easier for you to find the information you need and want. 

Focus on the Family exists to bring families closer to each other and to our Creator. Our sites are based on a set of foundational _Christian beliefs_ which you may want to review. We make no apologies for holding a Judeo-Christian perspective of marriage, family and the value of life and children. Thanks for your openness to respectfully consider our viewpoints. We appreciate your courtesy! To find out more about our organization, please visit About Us.

All we ask is that you agree to abide by the following Terms and Conditions. Take a few minutes to look them over because by using our sites you automatically agree to them. Naturally, if you don't agree, please do not use the sites. We reserve the right to make any modifications that we deem necessary at any time. Please continue to check these terms to see what those changes may be! Your continued use of the Focus on the Family Web sites means that you accept those changes.

## Restrictions on Use of Our Online Materials

All materials contained in the Focus on the Family Web sites ("Online Material") are the copyrighted property of Focus on the Family. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are proprietary to Focus on the Family. No Online Material from our Web sites may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, except that you may download one copy of the materials on any single computer for your personal, noncommercial home use only, provided that you 1) retain all copyright, trademark and propriety notices, 2) you make no modifications to the materials, 3) you do not use the materials in a manner that suggests an association with any of our products, services, events or brands, and 4) you do not download quantities of materials to a database, server, or personal computer for reuse for commercial purposes. You may not, however, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit or distribute our Online Material in any way or for any other purpose un
